export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which movie features a young boy named Ishaan struggling with studies but gifted in art?",
    option1: "Taare Zameen Par",
    option2: "Chhota Bheem",
    option3: "Koi Mil Gaya",
    option4: "Dangal",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie tells the story of an alien named Jadoo befriending a boy named Rohit?",
    option1: "PK",
    option2: "Koi Mil Gaya",
    option3: "Robot",
    option4: "Shrek",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "In which film does a girl train hard to become a wrestler with her fatherâ€™s help?",
    option1: "Mary Kom",
    option2: "Dangal",
    option3: "Chak De! India",
    option4: "Lagaan",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which film is about a kid and his magical red bicycle?",
    option1: "Bhootnath",
    option2: "Stanley Ka Dabba",
    option3: "Chillar Party",
    option4: "Gattu",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie features Amitabh Bachchan as a friendly ghost?",
    option1: "Bhootnath",
    option2: "Haunted",
    option3: "Go Goa Gone",
    option4: "Ra.One",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie is about a lunchbox and a boy who never brings his own lunch?",
    option1: "Stanley Ka Dabba",
    option2: "The Lunchbox",
    option3: "Chillar Party",
    option4: "Chhichhore",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie shows a group of kids fighting for their dog Bheedu?",
    option1: "Taare Zameen Par",
    option2: "Chillar Party",
    option3: "Hawaa Hawaai",
    option4: "Secret Superstar",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which film stars an inspiring young girl who wants to become a singer?",
    option1: "Secret Superstar",
    option2: "Dangal",
    option3: "Queen",
    option4: "Stanley Ka Dabba",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which movie tells the story of a boy who dreams of skating?",
    option1: "Gattu",
    option2: "Hawaa Hawaai",
    option3: "Chillar Party",
    option4: "Bhootnath",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which film features a school, a strict principal, and fun adventures by a group of kids?",
    option1: "Chhota Bheem",
    option2: "Taare Zameen Par",
    option3: "Makdee",
    option4: "Chhichhore",
    ans: 2,
  },
];
